ISAAC LITZENBERGER SAN FRANCISCO BAY AREA

 yak@isaacyakl.com +1-510-925-3175 isaacyakl.com github.com/isaacyakl in linkedin.com/in/isaacyakl

ABOUT

engineer with over 5 years of experience designing and developing web applications. Demonstrated ability to identify and create result-driven solutions; wrote the #1 most-used paintball trade-in web app of 2015-2016; created NPM-published CSS background randomizer library. Values teamwork, a positive attitude, integrity, and user experience. Seeking a full-time position.

SKILLS

JavaScript / TypeScript / NextJS / React / Jest / Babel / Shopify / Webpack / Handlebars / Git / GitHub / NPM / Vercel / Bootstrap / HTML / CSS / SCSS / Tailwind CSS / PHP / Python / C++ / Discord API / Twitch API / Figma / REST / SEO / SEM / SMM / Adobe Apps

EDUCATION

2020 — Bachelor of Science in **Business Administration,** General Management (Dean's List) **CSU East Bay**

COURSES

Computer Science I & II **CSU San Marcos**

Front-End Nanodegree Grow w/ Google

The Web Developer Bootcamp udemy.com

React For Beginners wesbos.com

Developing Innovative Ideas for New Companies

The University of Maryland

EXPERIENCE

08/2020 - Present

New Breed Paintball and Airsoft — Remote

- Developed website features; saved \$100s/mo in 3rd-party app subs
- Coded industry-leading, trade-in web app; mitigated follow-up clarification
- · Automated structured data generation; improved Google results
- Performed SEO tasks; increased clicks 400% and impressions 600%
- Generated average monthly revenue of \$2,000+

Tools: JavaScript Shopify Liquid JSON PHP Git Adobe Apps

Web Developer

03/2014 - 08/2016

YourPbFriend — Fremont, CA

- Wrote the #1 most-used paintball trade-in web app of 2015-2016
- Identified key website improvements; became #2 online paintball store
- Embedded YouTube content to educate and create value for customers
- Increased revenue 10x in 2 years by utilizing the Shopify ecosystem
- Created a used-gun, rating system calculator; increased buyer trust

Tools: <u>¡Query</u> <u>Shopify Liquid</u> <u>Bootstrap</u> <u>PHP</u> <u>Adobe Apps</u>

PROJECTS

bRando.js — Website Background Randomizer Library

- Automatically changes CSS backgrounds on any DOM element
- Published on NPM; downloaded hundreds of times per week
- 100% code coverage and API documentation

Tools: TypeScript Jest Webpack Babel Git

isaacyakl.com — Personal Website

- · Portfolio, web-based resume, and blog
- Work entries statically generated using remark.js and gray-matter
- · An experiment in using relative CSS units instead of breakpoints

Tools: NextJS TypeScript React TSX/JSX YAML Markdown Git

Remote Jackbox Player — Single-screen Jackbox Interface

- Mobile-first web app to find and play Jackbox games remotely for free
- Simultaneously watch a stream and use Jackbox.tv on one screen
- Uses Twitch API to find channels streaming Jackbox games

Tools: JavaScript Babel Tailwind CSS Twitch API JSON Git

Random Owen Wowson — Discord bot to send Owen Wilson clips

- Gets random Owen Wilson "wow" movie clips
- Makes use of the open-source Owen Wilson Wow API
- Includes a small HTTP status server

Tools: Python Discord API JSON Git hikari hikari-lightbulb